Miss me?
M3GAN 2.0 is a action, science fiction, thriller
film directed by Gerard Johnstone.
After the underlying tech for M3GAN is stolen and misused by a powerful defense contractor to create a military-grade weapon known as Amelia, M3GAN's
creator Gemma realizes that the only option is to resurrect M3GAN and give her a few upgrades, making her faster, stronger, and more lethal.
Gemma, played by Allison Williams.
Cady, played by Violet McGraw.
M3GAN, played by Amie Donald.
Christian Bradley, played by Aristotle Athari.
M3GAN (voice), played by Jenna Davis.
Cole, played by Brian Jordan Alvarez.
M3GAN 2.0 is a 2025 American science fiction action film written and directed
by Gerard Johnstone from a story he co-wrote with Akela Cooper.
A sequel to the 2022 film M3GAN and the second installment in the M3GAN franchise, the film stars Allison Williams, Violet McGraw,
Ivanna Sakhno, and Jemaine Clement, with Amie Donald physically portraying M3GAN while Jenna Davis voices the character.
Jason Blum and James Wan return as producers under their respective
Blumhouse Productions and Atomic Monster companies.
It follows M3GAN being rebuilt to combat a humanoid military robot built
using M3GAN's technology that is attempting an AI takeover.
M3GAN 2.0 premiered in New York on June 24, 2025, and was released
in North America by Universal Pictures on June 27.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and has grossed
$39.1 million against a budget of $15–25 million.
The film explores themes of android, artificial
intelligence (a.i.), fight, killer robot, beheading.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.